KAHO SHIBUYA

Frontend Developer React Developer

©	https://kahoshibuya.dev/
in	https://www.linkedin.com/in/kaho-shibuya/
()	https://github.com/shiv-chan
	kshibuya31@gmail.com
	604-499-7851

An aspiring **frontend developer** with a specialization in **React** development. A highly **passionate learner** and have worked on 5+ personal projects. With 3+ years of experience as a digital marketer, I value **user experience**, **promoting**, and **monetizing** web services. My professional background enables me to develop optimal frontend applications by enhancing **collaboration with the marketing and business teams** and seeing the product from a business standpoint.

EXPERIENCE

Puppy Time Vancouver - Web Designer & Web Developer

Apr 2021 - Aug 2021 | Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada

- Designed and developed the website from scratch including the page structure, theme, and UI/UX, which increased their brand awareness and achieved new clients.
- Collaborated with the marketing team and created the website SEO strategy-wise.
- Used: Squarespace, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Figma

sann, Inc. - Online Advertising Operation

Oct 2019 - Dec 2020 | Nagoya, Aichi, Japan

- Supported sales team with building ad campaign strategies by analyzing clients' past performances such as CPM or CPC or marketing trend data.
- Reported the results and suggested the next actions to the clients, which led to continuous contracts and incremental revenues.
- $^{\bullet}$ Created tools that reduced human-errors by ~90% and automated repetitive duties with Google products such as Sheets or Apps Script.
- Used: JavaScript (Google Apps Script)

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Go-to Pomodoro

- https://go-to-pomodoro.vercel.app/
- https://github.com/shiv-chan/go-to-pomodoro
- Built a responsive web app that the user can customize her/his own pomodoro timer with favourite BGM playing by embedded YouTube video player.
- Created a timer with minimal time logging.
- Composed Styled Components to change the theme colour according to its session.
- Used: React, Redux, IFrame Player API, Styled Component, Material UI, Figma

Weather App

- https://react-weather-app-peach-mu.vercel.app/
- https://github.com/shiv-chan/react-weather-app
- Implemented code with both Context API and Redux to see the difference.
- Fetched data from API asynchronously while passing a query using createAsyncThunk.
- Used: React, Redux, Open Weather API, Sass

EDUCATION

Cornerstone International Community College of Canada

Diploma, Web and Mobile App Development

Jan 2021 - Dec 2021 | Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada

• Related courses: Computing, Algorithms, Problem-solving, OOP, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node.js

Sprott Shaw College

Diploma, Business Admin Sales & Digital Marketing with Honours Feb 2015 - Jan 2016 | Kelowna, British Columbia, Canada | GPA 4.14

- Related courses: Bookkeeping, Accounting, Customer Services, Web design, SEO
- Practicum at Okanagan Boys and Girls Clubs as Digital Marketing Assistant